etoosindia.com 2017-12-31

# Free JEE & NEET Online Coaching | Video Lectures & Mock Test - EtoosIndia

#### Privacy Policy

* * *

etoosindia.com is a division of Etoos Academy Pvt Ltd. It is an online IIT JEE coaching portal endeavoring constantly to provide you with premium quality education in terms of high quality video lectures. Since we are strongly committed to your right to privacy, we have drawn a privacy statement in place with regard to the information we collect from you. 

We use a secure server for credit card transactions to protect the credit card information of our clients and Cookies are used to store the login information.

##### 1\. What information does etoosindia.com collect from you?

Our web portal incorporates various communication ways like email address, first and last name, Mobile no. etc. We are committed to gather only that information which we will require to help you serve better. 

##### 2\. How etoosindia.com uses the information it collects/tracks?

To fulfill your requirements for IIT JEE preparation in all manners we collect information from our qualified faculties to ensure quality.

##### 3\. With whom the site shares the information it collects/tracks?

We have a privacy policy that does not allow us to disclose any information with the third party. Your personal information in any manner will be secured under our privacy policy.

##### 4\. Do all visitors have to pay?

All users across India can browse our site free of cost for searching any course, faculty, article or feature offered by our web portal. You are liable to pay only when you purchase/renew a course.

##### 5\. How etoosindia.com team can contact you?

The etoosindia.com has trained staff members who may contact you for either services or sales through various communication medium like mobile no., landlines no., email, sms.
